FRANK SUMNER

CUSTOMER SUCCESS ENGINEER

DETAILS

ADDRESS

Orlando, Florida United States

PHONE

352-461-3258

EMAIL

sumnerfranklinm@gmail.com

PROJECTS

FitFolio

Dude, Wash My Car

Workday Planner

Weather Dashboard

SKILLS

SQL

React

JavaScript

REST API

MongoDB

MySQL

Git

CSS

Visual Design

SASS

Data Migration

PROFILE

Full-stack web developer with experience in creating functional and useful web applications. Experience in large scale data migration projects, solo and collaborative campaigns, and over 10 years of customer-facing support and service. Seeking a role as a Customer Success Engineer.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Senior Claims Adjuster, Bristol West Insurance

Orlando, Florida

May 2021 — Present

- Mitigated litigation and excess costs by expertly evaluating injuries and auto damage against industry standards.
- Created an efficiency-based SOP to ensure timely and accurate claim handling.
- Headed multiple projects including an office newsletter and a PTO initiative for backstopping work.

Project Manager - Logistics & Production, Forterra Building Products

Denver, Colorado

Dec 2019 — May 2021

- Collaborated with engineers, site owners, and sales to set reasonable expectations for project timelines.
- Prevented avoidable costs by maintaining Colorado Department of Transportation compliance for all company drivers.
- Set company location record monthly profit in February 2021 by maximizing production and shipping capabilities and negotiating third-party contracts

Document Control Specialist, Universal Creative

Orlando, Florida

Mar 2014 — Aug 2019

- Saved \$30MM by archiving and redistributing existing blueprints and plans, which prevented a ground-up build
- Maintained continuity of digital files to ensure naming standards, appropriate file location, and format standardization.
- Coordinated worldwide communication by delivering project files and documents including RFIs, submittals, deliverables, and comments.

EDUCATION

Full Stack Web Development Certificate, University of Central Florida

Orlando, Florida

Oct 2022 — May 2023

Bachelors Degree in History, University of Central Florida

Orlando, Florida

Aug 2014 — May 2020